LMs
Hello and welcome to our course
Functions, Tools and Agents with Lanchain
LMs have demonstrated an amazing ability
to interact with humans using natural language
which has opened the door to many new applications
But how can LMs also interact with our existing software infrastructure
For example, by letting it decide
when to make a function call to a different program
to get more information or to take an action
LMs were originally designed to generate text for humans
But some LMs have now been trained to output formatted data
such as values stored as JSON
to make it easy to let the LM decide
when to call other code as a subroutine
This significantly expands what you can do with LMs
such as let them extract information
from structured or tablet data
which LMs have typically struggled with
Here to tell you more about this is Harrison Chase
co-founder and CEO of Lanchain
who has also talked to two previous short courses
Welcome back Harrison
Thanks Andrew, so great to be back
You're right, this new capability
which OpenAI has named function calling
is really helpful for developers working with LLMs
Harrison, you've described Lanchain in other courses
but maybe you could describe what has changed
and what you'll be covering in this course
Absolutely, as you know Lanchain is an open source library
that helps developers bridge the gap between traditional software
and LLMs
It allows developers to support any number of different LLMs
and provides over 500 integrations to different language models
vector stores and tools
as well as supporting memory chains and agents
There are two significant changes that you will be getting into during the course
the first is the development of Lanchain expression language or LCEL
that makes composing components or chains simpler and more intuitive
the second is changes to take advantage of the new function calling capability
you'll learn how to use that directly
and will also show how it can be used to do tasks like tagging or extracting data
function calling makes building tools for LLMs simpler and more reliable
you'll build some tools and then use them to build a conversational agent
Agents can do complex multi-step reasoning
and can select tools to help them use and solve problems
you get to use all of those elements in the course
and in the final project
that sounds great Harrison
and I think this will be useful for many people
that want to learn to take advantage of these new advanced element capabilities
many people have worked to make this course possible
we're grateful to Lance Martin
and Nuno Kampus from Lanchain
and on the deep learning.ai side
Jeff Lodwick and Eshmael Gagari also contributed to this course
so that let's go on to the next video
and let's get started
先開始吧!